

ROBERT KLASSEN

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

LEARN ADAPT OPTIMIZE

CONTACT INFORMATION

Klassen.Rob@gmail.com 905-931-0432 https://www.RobKlassen.com www.linkedin.com/in/rob-klassen https://github.com/RobKlassen

SKILLS

Language Fundamentals:

- HTML5
- CSS / SCSS
- Javascript
- JQuery

Data Management:

- Firebase
- RESTful APIs

React:

- Components
- Props
- Classes
- Hooks

Working with Git:

- Version Control
- Collaboration
- GitHub

Team-based development Collaborative coding Responsive Design

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology AUG 2021 - OCT 2021 Immersive WebDev Bootcamp Accelerated JS + WebDev

Niagara College SEP 2011 - APR 2012 Winemaking & Viticultural Tech

Brock University SEP 2008 - JUNE 2009 General Sciences

ABOUT ME

Committed to bringing fresh perspective into the world of Front-End Web Development. My diverse background in work environments has equipped me with a unique perspective on problem solving, with a focus on optimization in the workflow and quickly adapting to changes in the workplace. My ability to communicate concisely and effectively has been an invaluable asset, as is my ability to organize data in an intuitive and sensible way.

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

TITLE OF MY THIRD PROJECT

GOAL OF THIS PROJECT

This is the description of my third project, it's a really great project that shows off all kinds of cool things which I'll be able to talk about when I'm assigned and complete my third project.

REGIONAL AIR QUALITY

COLLABORATIVE CODING AND ACCESSING APIS

After getting signage on project scope / pseudocode for project utilizing an API that logs current global air quality data, and producing results based on location and user query. Completed in collaborative setting, using SCSS, Vanilla Javascript, and focusing on version control with GitHub.

BEACHSTAYS

MATCH TEMPLATE GIVEN WITH ACCESSIBILITY AND RESPONSIVENE DESIGN

Given one of three layouts to work off, the purpose of the project was to match a design as closely as possible using SCSS (using variables, mixins, partial structure, and media queries). Mobile layout design was drafted and interpreted without guidance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FIVE ROWS CRAFT WINERY

Sales and Inventory Logistics | July 2020 - Sept 2021

Maintained inventory, oversaw online ordering through Shopify store, customer communication, shipping logistics, tasting bar.

NIAGARA OAST HOUSE BREWERY

Brewery Technician | Aug 2017 - Mar 2020

General brewery tech, filtering, tank transfers, CIP management, Basic Lab work, packaging / canning/ kegging / shipping, spreadsheet management

ELMWOOD FINE CUSTOM CABINETRY (CABICO)

Engineering Tech | Mar 2013 - Apr 2017

Interpreted and worked with cad drawings, programmed CNC machines for shop, managed material optimization software, maintained spreadsheets.